Now we're going to show you how to define and use your own enumerated type.
现在我们将向你展示如何定义和使用你自己的枚举类型。
At the top of the screen,
在屏幕顶部，
we take a color coded threat level of a standard security system,
我们采用标准安全系统的颜色编码的威胁级别，
and encoded into an enumerated type.
并编码为枚举类型。
There are five possible levels.
有五个可能的级别。
Low, guarded, elevated, high, and severe.
低、防守、升高、高和严重。
We can refer to these levels using exactly these words throughout our code.
我们可以在整个代码中使用这些单词来引用这些级别。
Next, there are two helper functions whose definitions we will show you later.
接下来，有两个辅助函数，我们稍后将向您展示其定义。
The first function is printThreat,
第一个函数是 PrintThreat，
which prints the string associated with the particular enumerated type.
它打印与特定枚举类型关联的字符串。
The second function is printShoes,
第二个功能是PrintShoes，
which prints whether a person is required to take
它可以打印在
off their shoes given the current threat level.
当前威胁等级下是否要求一个人脱鞋。
Our main, initializes a threat level,
我们的主函数，初始化威胁等级，
prints it out and then calls these two helper functions.
将其打印出来，然后调用这两个辅助函数。
Let's take a closer look at our enumerated type.
让我们仔细看看我们的枚举类型。
C creates a correspondence between each of these words and an integer value.
C 在每个单词和一个整数值之间创建对应关系。
So low has the value 0,
因此，低值的值为 0
and severe has the value 4.
，严重值为 4。
Notice how the function printThreat can refer to
请注意，函数 PrintThreat 如何在
these levels using exactly these words throughout its definition,
整个定义中使用这些单词来指代这些级别，这
making the code much easier to read,
使得代码更易于阅读，
printShoes does this as well.
PrintShoes 也可以做到这一点。在@@
Inside the main, we declare a new variable of type threat level T called, myThreat.
主体中，我们声明了一个名为 MyThreat 的威胁等级 T 的新变量。
We initialize this variable to the enum,
我们将这个变量初始化为枚举 HI
HIGH, which has the integer value 3.
GH，它的整数值为 3。
In order to print out the current threat level,
为了打印出当前的威胁级别，
we call the function, printThreat.
我们将函数称为 PrintThreat。
We create a stack frame for printThreat in which the argument,
我们为 PrintThreat 创建了一个堆栈框架，其中
myThreat, will be referred to as threat.
将参数 myThreat 称为威胁。
We mark the call site location and step into print threat.
我们标记呼叫地点位置并进入打印威胁。
Inside print threat, there is a switch statement which checks
在 print threat 中，有一个 switch 语句可以检查
the value of the threat and jumps to the corresponding case.
威胁的价值并跳转到相应的案例。
Here, we're jumping to case HIGH.
在这里，我们跳到了案例高位。
Inside of this case,
在本例中，
we print Orange/High, and the break exits us from the switch statement.
我们打印 Orange/High，中断使我们退出了 switch 语句。
Now we return to the function that called printThreat, which is our main.
现在我们回到名为 PrintThreat 的函数，这是我们的主函数。
Upon returning, the stack frame for printThreat is destroyed.
返回后，PrintThreat 的堆栈帧将被销毁。
Next, we execute the call to printShoes,
接下来，我们执行对 PrintShoes 的调用，
creating a stack frame for print shoes,
为打印鞋创建一个堆栈框架，
in which the argument, myThreat,
其中参数 myThreat
is referred to as currThreat.
被称为 currThreat。
We mark the call site location,
我们标记呼叫地点的位置，
and step into print shoes.
然后进入印花鞋。
Inside printShoes, there is an if/else statement.
在 PrintShoes 中，有一个 if/else 语句。
The if clause tests whether the current threat is greater than or equal to elevated.
if 子句用于测试当前威胁是否大于或等于已升级。
In this case, we're testing whether 3 is greater than or equal to 2.
在本例中，我们正在测试 3 是否大于或等于 2。
Since it is, we step into the then clause,
既然如此，我们进入了 then 条款，
print out the message,
打印出消息，
Please take off your shoes,
请脱鞋，
and exit the clause.
然后退出该条款。
Now we return to the function that called print shoes, which is our main.
现在我们回到名为 print shoes 的函数，这是我们的主函数。
Upon returning, the stack frame for print shoes is destroyed.
返回后，印花鞋的堆叠框架被销毁。
Finally, the program exits the main,
最后，程序退出主节点
and its stack frame is destroyed.
，其堆栈帧被销毁。
Notice how much easier the code is to read because we've used an enumerated type.
请注意，由于我们使用了枚举类型，因此代码更容易阅读。
If instead, we had an int called,
相反，我们有一个名为 t
threat_level, with values 0 through 4.
hreat_level 的整数，其值为 0 到 4。
The code would be littered with a lot of numbers
代码中会充斥着很多数字，
whose meaning might be unclear to the reader.
读者可能不清楚其含义。
Enumerated types make it easier to read,
枚举类型使读取
write, and modify code.
、编写和修改代码变得更加容易。